celebmafia.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy & Cookies Policy - CelebMafia

CelebMafia, Inc. has created this privacy statement to describe our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: “celebmafia.com” at [https://celebmafia.com](https://celebmafia.com/). We seek to protect your private information so that you have a pleasurable viewing experience on our Web site. We will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. Please return to this page from time to time, as we will be updating this statement as our services continue to grow. We welcome and encourage questions, comments, and suggestions. Please contact us at celebmafia[at]yandex.com with any questions.

## Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

## Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies store information about your use of a particular Web site or service and are typically used to make services more convenient and personalized. Most cookies are “session cookies,” which are automatically deleted whenever you leave a Web site, although some cookies remain on your computer until you remove them.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser(s) (i.e. Gorilla Nation, MTVN, Brightroll, Adconion, Google, Tribal Fusion, Husky Media Advertising.com, DoubleClick and/or others) may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

## How We Use Cookies

We use cookies

  * (1) to estimate the number of visitors to our Web site
  * (2) to measure general traffic patterns, and
  * (3) to personalize information and services we provide to you on the site.

Companies that place ads on the celebmafia.com Web site — including, but not limited to Tribal Fusion, AOL Advertising.com, LiJit, BurstMedia (Blinx), MTVN, Brightroll, Adconion, Google, Husky Media Advertising.com, DoubleClick and/or others — may also use their own cookies to help determine the frequency and placement of particular ads. Your browser controls how cookies are used and can be set to not allow them. However, it is possible that some parts of the celebmafia.com site may not function properly if your browser refuses our cookies. We may, from time to time, use cookies to store your zip code and email address for use with certain current or future services such as e-mail update list(s), showtimes e-mail services, local showtimes profiles, theater and movie preference profiles.

## Cookie Notification and Disabling

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see [aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/). You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.

## Personally Identifiable Information

**What Personally Identifiable Information Is**  
Personally identifiable information is your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information.

## Where We Collect Personally Identifiable Information

celebmafia.com collects personally identifiable information when you (1) subscribe to our mailing list(s), (2) submit feedback, questions, or “contact us” messages.

## How We Use Personally Identifiable Information

celebmafia.com uses your personally identifiable information to personalize your experience on our Web site, to deliver products and/or services ordered and/or purchased by you and to contact you. CelebMafia.com also compiles aggregate data from all of our customers to prepare internal reports about which pages are popular, how many total unique users visit our site, and different traffic patterns. CelebMafia.com does not combine your personally identifiable information with information about pages visited, purchases made, or any other click-stream data.

## Who We Disclose Personally Identifiable Information To

celebmafia.com will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. celebmafia.com may disclose some personal information to outside companies who help celebmafia.com with the administration and delivery of newsletters, promotional games, trivia contests, and sweepstakes. For example, a company who administers a sweepstakes for us may use your e-mail address to update you on your status in the sweepstakes. Or, our newsletters may be distributed by another company that will use your e-mail or shipping address for delivery. The celebmafia.com Web site contains links to other Web sites. Although we do not provide any personally identifiable information to these companies, we cannot guarantee your privacy once you leave the celebmafia.com Web site. celebmafia.com is not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of Web sites with links on our site. celebmafia.com may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement personnel, government officials, or others when we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent violations of the law, injury to person or property, or any harm to celebmafia.com or others.

## Communication

We collect personally identifiable information such as first and last name and email address when you sign up for our email list(s). These email services provide celebmafia.com users free opt-in updates about the celebmafia.com site and movie information and/or content. We may also request secondary information, such as your movie preferences, which we will use to help personalize the site for you in the future. We may also on occasion send promotional and informational mail to you from celebmafia.com. You may opt-out of receiving these secondary communications by sending an email with “remove” in the subject line to celebmafia[at]yandex.com .

## Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Demographic Information

Demographic information may be collected on the web site. The information will only be shared with any third-parties in an aggregate format.

## Public Forums

This site makes voting and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal opinion. Personally identifiable information is not made available to the public or to other users and voting is anonymous. However, when using message boards, your user name and email address – which constitutes personally identifiable information, provided by you, is made available on the message boards.

## Log Files

celebmafia.com, both using its own systems and the systems of others (such as Google or Quantcast, among others) automatically logs information such as IP addresses, ISPs, and browser type but does not link that information to personally identifying information. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

## Sharing of Information

celebmafia.com is engaged in “powered by” relationships as more fully described herein. celebmafia.com does not share any personally identifiable information with third-parties, other than its partners as herein described, and will otherwise only share information in aggregate form. We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies from banner ads are collected by advertising networks, and we do not have access to this information.

## Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Subject to your consent, Exponential Interactive, Inc collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. You may change your consent decision at any time via . For more details including access requests and complaints, review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com).

Exponential Cookie Details:

## Disclosure Regarding Google Display Advertising

We implement Google Analytics features that use Display Advertising information for Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, by going to the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

We, along with third-party vendors (including Google), use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookies) to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website. You can read more about the cookies used by Google Analytics advertising features, by going to the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Employees are notified in staff meetings of security policies and practices regularly. Access to data limited and employees obtain access to log files by a secured password. celebmafia periodically reviews web security and ensures that all policies and practices are adhered to within the company.

## Children

**Our Policy For Guests Under Age 18** celebmafia.com is committed to protecting the privacy of children. We encourage parents and guardians to explore the Internet with their children. Visitors under age 18 should not submit any personally identifiable information to celebmafia.com.

## Links

celebmafia.com site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are ‘clicking’ to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

## Correct/Update or Cancel Subscription

Users can change their information with celebmafia.com by emailing a request to celebmafia[at]yandex.com . If you wish to unsubscribe from any celebmafia mailing list, please email celebmafia[at]yandex.com using the e-mail address you would like removed and type “UNSUBSCRIBE” as the subject of the message.

## Notification of Changes

celebmafia.com privacy practices may change periodically. celebmafia.com will notify users of changes only if the information collected from the user differs from that stated at the time of collection. celebmafia.com may also obtain the user’s consent by posting notice on the site.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact celebmafia: Email: celebmafia[at]yandex.com
